

FAROOQ AZIZ

- +92316-2300835
- dev-farooq-portfolio.vercel.app
- github.com/cl-farooqaziz
- in linkedIn.com/in/farooq-aziz-b09b40223

Summary

Skilled Front-End Developer with 2 years of experience. I'm passionate about Branding and creating attractive Responsive Websites using HTML, CSS, JS & Bootstrap. To secure a responsible career opportunity to fully utilize my skills, while making a significant contribution to the success of the company.

Skills

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- Bootstrap, Tailwind
- React Js, Next Js
- GitHub, Firebase
- PSD, XD
- Payment Integration
- API Integration
- Form validation

Languages

• English, Urdu, Balochi

Experience

FRONT-END DEVELOPER CRYSTALLITE DIGITAL PVT, KARACHI	2022 - PRESENT
FRONT-END DEVELOPER – (INTERN) JAWAN PAKISTAN, KARACHI	2021 - 2021
COURIER TEAM LEAD MOVEX LOGISTIC COURIER, KARACHI	2020 - 2021
CREW TRAINER MCDONALD'S PAKISTAN, KARACHI	2017 - 2020

Education

INDUS UNIVERSITY, KARACHI

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering

GOVT ATTA SHAD DEGREE COLLAGE, QUETTA

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering

Certifications

WEB & MOBILE APP DEVELOPMENT JAWAN PAKISTAN, KARACHI

HTML5 & CSS3

PIRPLE.COM

WORDPRESS

DIGISKILLS TRAINING PROGRAM

CERTIFIED INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

GLOBAL COMPUTER INSTITUTE, KARACHI